Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
I was alone on holidays.
كنت وحدي في العطلة.
At school
في المدرسة
or at home,
أو في المنزل،
I always felt lonely.
لقد شعرت بالوحدة دائمًا.
He has everything,
لديه كل شيء
but he is still alone.
ولكنه لا يزال وحيدا.
In the end,
في النهاية،
we're the same, both lonely.
نحن نفس الشيء، كلانا وحيد.
Would you like
هل ترغب في ذلك؟
a warm drink?
مشروب دافئ؟
Can't believe
لا أستطيع أن أصدق
it's a one-month contract.
إنه عقد لمدة شهر واحد.
They were usually just
كانوا عادة فقط
one-night stands,
علاقات ليلة واحدة،
relationships
العلاقات
that disintegrate by dawn.
التي تتحلل مع الفجر.
But you
ولكنك
actually
في الحقيقة
gave this a month.
أعطى هذا شهرًا.
You were serious
لقد كنت جادًا
and sincere.
وصادقة.
I could tell by your eyes.
أستطيع أن أقول ذلك من خلال عينيك.
It's an earnestness
إنها جدية
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
I should've refused you.
كان ينبغي علي أن أرفضك.
That's my usual style.
هذا هو أسلوبي المعتاد.
But I don't know why
ولكنني لا أعرف السبب
I felt drawn
لقد شعرت بالانجذاب
to the "one month."
"إلى شهر واحد".
Yeah.
نعم.
Mom.
أم.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Got it.
فهمتها.
I've found the best doctor too.
لقد وجدت أفضل طبيب أيضًا.
Don't worry about money.
لا تقلق بشأن المال.
I've also
انا ايضا
taken care of my tuition.
اهتم بدروسي.
I'm not a kid anymore.
أنا لم أعد طفلاً بعد الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
Bye.
الوداع.
I love you.
أحبك.
He didn't meet anyone today, did he?
لم يقابل أحدًا اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
Good.
جيد.
Keep monitoring him.
استمر بمراقبته.
So I see your spy's just
لذا أرى أن جاسوسك فقط
reported my whereabouts to you.
لقد أبلغتك بمكان تواجدي.
Before that,
قبل ذلك،
have a look at this.
إلق نظرة على هذا.
It's a new contract
إنه عقد جديد
for another month.
لشهر آخر.
I've adjusted the terms.
لقد قمت بتعديل الشروط.
Jaehun-hyung,
جايهون هيونغ،
just one more month.
شهر واحد فقط
It'll only
سوف فقط
cost you 10,000 dollars.
سيكلفك 10000 دولار.
I'll do anything you want.
سأفعل أي شيء تريده.
Anything.
أي شئ.
Jaehun-hyung!
جيهون هيونغ!
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
You only have wine and salad every day.
كل يوم لا تأكل سوى النبيذ والسلطة.
Eat something regular at times.
تناول شيئا عاديا في بعض الأحيان.
What kind of service do you want tonight?
ما نوع الخدمة التي تريدها الليلة؟
Haejun is always smiling.
هايجون يبتسم دائمًا.
His smile is so bright that
ابتسامته مشرقة جداً لدرجة أن
this thing we have almost feels real.
هذا الشيء الذي لدينا يبدو حقيقيًا تقريبًا.
But I found out by chance today
ولكنني اكتشفت ذلك بالصدفة اليوم
that beneath his smile
أن تحت ابتسامته
is a heavy heart.
هو قلب ثقيل.
He shoulders so much alone,
إنه يتحمل الكثير بمفرده،
yet he always greets me with a warm smile.
ومع ذلك فهو يستقبلني دائمًا بابتسامة دافئة.
When I knew of his troubled soul,
عندما عرفت عن روحه المضطربة،
I began to feel for him a little.
بدأت أشعر به قليلاً.
Now,
الآن،
I want to protect his smile.
أريد أن أحمي ابتسامته.
Even just a little,
حتى ولو قليلا
I'll be more gentle.
سوف أكون أكثر لطفا.